welcome back in this week's you learn to
欢迎回来 本周的视频你将学习
implement a neural network before diving
如何实现一个神经网络
into the technical details I wanted in
在我们深入学习具体技术之前
this video to give you a quick overview
我希望快速的带你预览一下
of what you'll be seeing in this week's
本周你将会学到的东西
videos so if you don't follow all the
如果这个视频中的某些细节
details in this video don't worry about
你没有看懂 不用担心
it we'll delve in the technical details
我们将在后面的几个视频中
in the next few videos but for now let's
深入讨论技术细节 现在我们
give a quick overview of how you
开始快速浏览一下如何
implement in your network last week we
实现神经网络
had talked about logistic regression and
上周我们讨论了logistic回归
we saw how this model corresponds to the
我们了解了这个模型如何
following computation graph where you
与下面这个计算图建立联系
need to put the features X and parameters
你需要输入特征X
w and b that allows you to compute z which
参数w和b 然后你就可以计算出z
is then used to compute a and we were
接下来使用z计算出a
using a interchangeably with this output
我们将a的符号换为表示输出的y^
Y hat and then you can compute the loss
接下来计算损失函数l
function l a neural network looks like this
神经网络就是这个样子
and as I'd already previously alluded
我之前已经提到过了
you can form a neural network by
你可以把
stacking together a lot of little
许多sigmoid单元堆叠起来
sigmoid units whereas previously this
形成一个神经网络
node corresponds to two steps of
这个节点包含了之前讲的计算的两个步骤
calculations the first three compute the
首先 计算出z值
z value second is it computes this a
然后计算a值
value in this neural network this stack of
这个神经网络中
notes will correspond to a Z like
这些节点首先
calculation like this as well as an a
像这样计算z
like calculation like that and then that
接着像这样计算a
node will correspond to another Z and
这个节点同样
another a like calculation so the
计算了z和a
notation which we should use later will
因此 我们稍后会使用
look like this
下面这些记号
first what inputs the features X
首先 X表示输入特征
together with some parameters W and b
W和b是参数
and this will allow you to compute z1 so
通过这些计算出z1
new notation that one should use is that
我们会使用新的符号
we'll use a superscript square bracket 1
上标 方括号 1
to refer to quantities associated with
表示与这些节点相关的数
this stack of nodes called a layer and
这些节点被称为一层
then later we'll use superscript square
我们用上标
bracket 2 to refer to quantities
方括号 2 表示
associated with that really that's
和这个节点相关的数
called another layer of the network and
这是网络的另一个层
the superscript square brackets like we
我们这里使用的上标方括号
have here are not to be confused with
不会和我们之前用来表示
the superscript round brackets which we
单个的训练样本的
used to refer to individual training
上标圆括号混淆
examples so whereas X
就是说我使用
supersu round bracket I referred to the
X上标圆括号表示
Ith trained example superscript square
第i个训练样本
bracket 1 and 2 refers to these
上标方括号1 2
different layers layer 1 and layer 2
表示不同的层 这是网络的第一层
in this network but they're going on
这是第二层
after computing z1 similar to logistic
类似logistic回归
regression there will be a computation
在计算了z1后
to compute a1 and that's just some
需要使用sigmoid(z1)计算a1
sigmoid of z1 and then you compute z2
接下来你需要使用
using another linear equation and then
另外一个线性方程计算z2
compute a2 and a2 is the final output
接着计算a2 a2就是整个神经网络
of the neural network and will also be
最终的输出
used interchangeably with Y hat so I
我用y^表示网络的输出
know there was a lot of details but the
我知道其中有很多细节
key intuition to take away is that
有一点非常难以理解
whereas for logistic regression we had
logistic回归中
this z followed by a calculation and
z后面直接计算a
this neural network here we just do it
而这个神经网络中
multiple times as a z followed by a
我们只是反复的计算z
calculation and a z followed by a
然后计算a 然后又计算z 然后又计算a
calculation and then you finally compute
最后你得到了最终的输出
the loss at the end and you remember
你应该记得
that for the logistic regression we had in
在logistic中
some backward calculation in order to
有一些从后向前的计算
compute derivatives they computing
用来计算导数
da dz and so on so in the same way in
da dz等 同样
a neural network we'll end up doing a
在神经网络中
backward calculation that looks like
我们也有从后向前的计算
this and we jump you end up computing
看起来就像这样
da2 dz2 that allows you to compute so
你把da2 dz2计算出来之后
dw2 db2 and so on in this order the right
才能计算dw2 db2等
to left backward calculation that is
按红色箭头表示的那样
denoting with the red arrows
从右到左反向计算
So that's quick overview of what a neural network
刚才只是带你大概了解了一下神经网络
looks like but we take the logistic
大概是什么样子的 我们把logistic回归
regression and repeating it twice I know
重复两次
there was a lot of new notation lot of
我清楚多了很多新的符号
new details don't worry about to get and
新的细节 不用担心如果你没有理解
follow everything we'll go into the
在接下来的视频中
details most slowly in the next few
我们会仔细的讨论具体细节
videos so let's go on to the next video
继续看下一个视频吧
we'll stop to talk about the neural
我们将会开始讨论
network representation
神经网络的表示